https://www.firstmooselake.com/about/privacy-policy/

Checking
Regular CheckingRewards CheckingStudent Rewards CheckingInterest Checking
Savings
Statement SavingsStudent Statement SavingsSilver Dollar Saver SavingsInvestors Money Market Savings
Cards
Consumer Credit CardConsumer Debit CardPre-Paid VISA® Cards
Loans
Overdraft ProtectionAutos, Airplanes & RecreationalReal Estate & Mortgage LoansHome Equity Line Of Credit (HELOC)
Certificates of DepositIndividual Retirement Account (IRAs)
Business
Business CheckingBusiness SavingsCommercial Loans
Merchant Card ServicesBusiness VISA® Credit CardRemote Deposit
InvestmentsResources
Agate Financial Services(opens in new window/tab)ATMsCollege AveDisclosuresFraud Prevention
Lost or Stolen CardMoose Lake Area Chamber of CommerceRatesReorder ChecksFee Schedule
About
Contact & LocationsMission and Vision StatementFirst National Bank of Moose Lake HistoryBoard of Directors
Real Estate Loans
Home Equity Line Of Credit (HELOC)
Certificates of Deposit
Individual Retirement Account (IRAs)
FACTS
WHAT DOES FIRST NATIONAL BANK OF MOOSE LAKE DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number
Account balances and payment history
Credit history and credit scores
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information, the reasons First National Bank of Moose Lake chooses to share, and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does FIRST NATIONAL BANK OF MOOSE LAKE share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
No
We don’t share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –Information about your transactions and experiences
No
We don’t share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –information about your creditworthiness
No
We don’t share
For our affiliates to market to you
No
We don’t share
For non-affiliates to market to you
No
We don’t share
Questions?
Call (218)485-4441, Toll Free: (866) 333-4441 or go to www.firstmooselake.com
Who We Are
Who is providing this notice?
First National Bank of Moose Lake of Moose LakeMain Office:  400 Elm Avenue, Moose Lake, MN 55767Branch Office:  20 Hartman Drive, Moose Lake, MN 55767
What we do
How does First National Bank of Moose Lake protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does First National Bank of Moose Lake collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or deposit money
pay your bills or apply for a loan
use your credit or debit card
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
First National Bank of Moose Lake has no affiliates.
Non-affiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
First National Bank of Moose Lake does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products to you.
Paying for college can be stressful. See how College Ave can help.
Learn More
Visa® Platinum Credit Card
Hometown convenience with worldwide acceptance. Start your consumer or commercial application today.
Apply Now
Online Home Loan Application
Looking to buy, build or refinance your dream home? Our convenient online applications fit with your busy life.
Apply Now
Online Consumer Loan Application
Ready for a new vehicle? Looking at purchasing an ATV? Our online application can help you get started.
Our amazing staff donated a total of $660.00 to the Moose Lake Police Department! Staff could pay $10.00 to wear...
We had beautiful weather to complete our Fall highway clean-up. Our staff take pride in our community and enjoy giving...
Community bank provides local hospital critical access to PPP funding By Matt Doffing COVID-19 could not have struck at a...
Ask us about ID Theftsmart! ID Theftsmart is an identity theft protection and credit monitoring service we offer at First...
Our annual Shred Event brought in 4,852 pounds of paper to shred for our customers!  Thank you to everyone who came...
Read More
